Guide to the Lynne Tillman Papers 1939-2008 (Bulk 1984-2006) MSS 180 MSS 180
© 2012 Fales Library and Special Collections
Lynne Tillman Papers
Bulk, 1984-2006
1923-2006
MSS 180
© 2012 Fales Library and Special Collections
65.62 linear feet
Lynne Tillman has been an influential writer, filmmaker, and art critic in the downtown New York art scene. This collection includes correspondence with other artists and writers, materials relating to the creation and publication of her books, financial papers, various publications including Tillman's short stories, articles, and interviews, and educational materials. This collections puts Tillman's work into the context of her education and personal and professional relationships.
Tillman, Lynne
Bibliography
Lynne Tillman has published widely. In addition to her novels and non-fiction books she is the author of numerous stories and essays published in anthologies, magazines, catalogues, and as collections of her work. Below is a list of her fiction and non-fiction books.
Madame Realism. Illustrated by Kiki Smith. New York: The Print Center, 1984.
Haunted Houses. New York: Poseidon Press, 1987.
Absence Makes the Heart. London: Serpent’s Tail, 1990
Motion Sickness. New York: Poseidon Press, 1991
Cast In Doubt. New York: Poseidon Press. 1992
The Madame Realism Complex. New York: Semiotexte, 1992.
Living with Contradictions. Drawings by Jane Dickson. Buffalo, NY: Hallwalls, 1993.
Haunted Houses. New York: High Risk Books, 1995.
The Velvet Years: Warhol’s Factory 1965-1967. New York: Thunder’s Mouth Press, 1995.
The Broad Picture: Essays 1987-1996. New York: Serpent’s Tail, 1997.
No Lease on Life: A Novel. New York: Harcourt Brace, 1997.
Bookstore: The Life and Times of Jeannette Watson and Books and Co. New York: Harcourt Brace, 1999.
This is Not It: Stories. New York: Distributed Art Publishers, 2002.
American Genius, a comedy. New York: Soft Skull Press, 2006.
Related Archival Materials note
Serpent's Tail/High Risk Books Archive, MSS 86
Ira Silverberg Papers, MSS 110
Martha Wilson Papers (unprocessed)
Sylver Lotringer Papers and Semiotext(e) Archive (unprocessed)
Biographical Note
Lynne Tillman is a writer, filmmaker, and cultural critic. Tillman grew up in Woodmere, Long Island and came to New York City to study painting, literature and history at Hunter College. After graduating she lived in Europe for 6 years, moving between London and Amsterdam and taking part in the avant-garde film scene as a filmmaker and organizer. While in Europe she compiled a collection of writings by Americans living abroad. This book, titled Americans Abroad, was never published despite having two publishers and numerous noteworthy contributors including Paul Bowles and William Burroughs. While abroad Tillman also wrote for the Dutch sex magazine Suck, and began writing her short novel, Weird Fucks.
Tillman returned to New York in 1976 and continued making films. In 1984 Tillman and Sheila McLaughlin released Committed, their film about Frances Farmer's life, family relationships and institutionalization. The film received partial funding from the Jerome Foundation and Channel Four (London) and screened at numerous film festivals, including its premier at the Berlin Film Festival. She also wrote a screenplay adaptation of Jane Bowles's novel, Two Serious Ladies. Although she obtained funding to make the film and permission from Paul Bowles, a conflict with a European publisher over the copyright prevented the project's completion.
In between filmmaking and working Lynne Tillman co-edited "Paranoids Anonymous Newsletter" (P.A.N.) an experimental literary newspaper that ran for three editions, and began writing her first published book, Haunted Houses (1987). The novel follows three young women coming of age in the United States during the 1950s and 1960s. In addition to her writing and filmmaking between 1981 and 1987, Lynne Tillman completed the required coursework for a doctorate in sociology at CUNY Graduate School. This coursework enabled Tillman to explore topics and texts that she felt were underrepresented in her education. Lynne Tillman formed rich relationships not just with her contemporaries but also with artists and writers from preceding creative paradigms including the surrealists Meret Oppenheim, Paul Bowles, and Charles Henri Ford. These relationships often began as creative opportunities for Tillman. In the case of Meret Oppenheim, Tillman conducted, edited and published an interview with the artist about women and surrealism. With Paul Bowles she requested some unpublished material for the Americans Abroad anthology. This request and her interest in his and his wife Jane's work lead to a long correspondence and eventual meeting in Tangiers. In each case the relationships provided inspiration and guidance.
Tillman also drew from her experiences and professional and personal networks to mentor emerging artists. She has been a creative writing instructor at Bard, Princeton, and SUNY Albany.
Bibliography
Madame Realism. Illustrated by Kiki Smith. New York: The Print Center, 1984.
Haunted Houses. New York: Poseidon Press, 1987.
Absence Makes the Heart. London: Serpent’s Tail, 1990
Motion Sickness. New York: Poseidon Press, 1991
Cast In Doubt. New York: Poseidon Press. 1992.
The Madame Realism Complex. New York: Semiotexte, 1992.
Living with Contradictions. Drawings by Jane Dickson. Buffalo, NY: Hallwalls, 1993.
Haunted Houses. New York: High Risk Books, 1995.
The Velvet Years: Warhol’s Factory 1965-1967. New York: Thunder’s Mouth Press, 1995.
The Broad Picture: Essays 1987-1996. New York: Serpent’s Tail, 1997.
No Lease on Life: A Novel. New York: Harcourt Brace, 1997.
Bookstore: The Life and Times of Jeannette Watson and Books and Co. New York: Harcourt Brace, 1999.
This is Not It: Stories. New York: Distributed Art Publishers, 2002.
American Genius: A Comedy. New York: Soft Skull Press, 2006
Separated Materials note
Lynne Tillman's book library has been separated from the archival materials. Some of these materials have been catalogued into Fales Special Collections holdings. These items can be located through Bobcat, NYU's online catalog, by searching for "Lynne Tillman". An inventory of all the separated materials can be viewed here.
Arrangement note
Folders are genreally arranged alphabetically. The collection is arranged into twenty-one series.
Series I: Correspondence
Series II: Subject Files
Series III: Administrative Materials
Series IV: Committed (1984)
Series V: Haunted Houses (1987)
Series VI: Motion Sickness (1991)
Series VII: Cast in Doubt (1992)
Series VIII: The Velvet Years (1995)
Series IX: No Lease on Life (1997)
Series X: Bookstore (1999)
Series XI: American Genius (2006)
Series XII: Essay and Story Collections
Series XIII: Other Works and Activities
Series XIV: Education
Series XV: Printed Material
Series XVI: Posters
Series XVII: Film
Series XVIII: Video
Series XIX: Audio
Series XX: Computer Disks
Series XXI: Objects
Scope and Content
The Lynne Tillman Papers document Lynne Tillman's professional career as a novelist, filmmaker and cultural critic. The collection represents her creative process including the development of written and film works through subject files, notes, drafts, and page proofs. Correspondence with artists, writers, and intellectuals comprises another significant component of the collection. In addition to personal and family relationships, these materials document Lynne Tillman's relationships with surrealist artists including Meret Oppenheim, Paul Bowles, and Charles Henri Ford as well as her collegial and mentoring relationships with artists such as Susan Hiller, Jessica Stockholder, and Martha Wilson among others. A small part of the collection documents Lynne Tillman's education through high-school year books and course materials. While the collection materials span the years 1901 to 2006, the bulk of the material represents the years 1984-2006.
Access Restrictions
Open to researchers. Appointments are necessary for the use of manuscript and archival collections.
Provenance
The collection was acquired by NYU in 2006.
A.I.R. Gallery (New York, N.Y.).; Acker, Kathy, 1948-1997; Bowles, Paul, 1910-1999; Cooper, Dennis, 1953-; Ford, Charles Henri; Glück, Robert; Hiller, Susan; Holman, Bob, 1948-; Lotringer, Sylvère; McGrath, Patrick, 1950-; Oppenheim, Meret, 1913-1985; Rainer, Yvonne, 1934-; Rattray, David; Semiotext(e).; Serpent’s Tail (Firm).; Tillman, Lynne; Warhol, Andy, 1928-1987; Wilson, Martha, 1947-; Audiocassettes.; Clippings (information artifacts); Feminism.; Lower East Side (New York, N.Y.) |v Fiction.; New York (N.Y.); Personal correspondence.; Postmodernism (Literature) |z New York (State) |z New York.; Women novelists.
- Series I: Correspondence
  Arrangement
  Subseries A and D are arranged alphabetically by last name, while Subseries B is arranged alphabetically by first name or first letter whenever possible. Subseries C is arranged chronologically.
  Scope and Content
  Series I: Correspondence follows Lynne Tillman's contact with family and friends, including artists, writers, and intellectuals. These materials document Lynne Tillman's relationships with surrealist artists including Meret Oppenheim, Paul Bowles, and Charles Henri Ford as well as her collegial and mentoring relationships with artists such as Susan Hiller, Jessica Stockholder, and Martha Wilson. The series is divided into four subseries:
  A: Individuals and Institutions
  B: Incomplete Names / Illegible / Unsigned
  C: Sent by Lynne Tillman
  D: Correspondence Files
  - Series I, Subseries A: Individuals and Institutions
    - A.R.T. Press / Rodney Sappington, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Aaron, Michele, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Abbott, Steve, 1988-1991 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - ABC No Rio, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Aberdein, Anna-Mai, Undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Abner Stein, 1989-1999 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - The Abortion Project, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Abruzzo, Paul, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Acker, Kathy ***see also*** Trip Street Press, 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Ackerman, Carol, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Acme Journal, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Acocella, Joan, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Adams, Megan, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Adnah, Eiel, 1994-1997 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Ahearn, Charlie and Jane Dickson, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Aherne, Patrick, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Albery, Nicholas, 1976-1999 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Alexander, China, [2000] (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Alexander, Nicholas, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Ali, Agha Shahid, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Alphabet City, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Aminoff, Judith (Gintz-), 1987-2002 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Amirthanayagam, Indran, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Anderson, Evan, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Andre, Michael, 1978-2005 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Andy Warhol Museum, 1994-1995 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Angell, Callie, 1994-2001 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Annedey, Jae[s], 1994 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - Anyone Corporation, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - AP Watt Ltd: Literary Agents, 1994-1997 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - Aperture, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - Aranda, Carlos, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - Arcimboldo, Giuseppe, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - Arnoldi, Katherine, Undated (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - Aronson, Steven M.L., 2005 (Box 1, Folder 35)
    - Art + Commerce, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - Art & Understanding, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 37)
    - Art in America, 1987-1994 (Box 1, Folder 38)
    - art Moving International Inc., Undated (Box 1, Folder 39)
    - Art Center, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 40)
    - Art Projekt, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 41)
    - Art Start, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 42)
    - Artforum, 1981-2001 (Box 1, Folder 43)
    - A.I.R. Gallery (Artists in Residence Gallery), 2005 (Box 1, Folder 44)
    - Artpaper, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 45)
    - Ashford, Doug, Undated (Box 1, Folder 46)
    - AMES (Asociacion de Mujeres de El Salvador), 1986 (Box 1, Folder 47)
    - Assemblage: A Critical Journal of Architecture and Design Culture, 1992-1993 (Box 1, Folder 48)
    - Auder, Michel, Undated (Box 1, Folder 49)
    - Ault, Julie, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 50)
    - Austin, Charles, 1984-1987 (Box 1, Folder 51)
    - Avec Books, 2002-2003 (Box 1, Folder 52)
    - Avillez, Martin, Undated (Box 1, Folder 53)
    - Ayrton, Carla and Sarah, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 54)
    - Bade, Paddy, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 55)
    - Baden, Mowry, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 56)
    - Bailey, Dave, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 57)
    - Baker, Aidan, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 58)
    - Baldessari, John, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 59)
    - Balken, Debra, 1992-1993 (Box 1, Folder 60)
    - Barker, Stephen, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 61)
    - Bartlett, Neil, 1993-2004 (Box 1, Folder 62)
    - Barton, Nancy, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 63)
    - Bassara, Robert, 1995-2000 (Box 1, Folder 64)
    - Bates, Bessie, 2000-2002 (Box 1, Folder 65)
    - Bates, Charlie, Julie, Scott & Jeff, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 66)
    - Batterham, David, 1980-2000 (Box 1, Folder 67)
    - Bauer, Jerry, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 68)
    - Baugh, Chris, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 69)
    - Beatt, Cynthia, 1977-1988 (Box 1, Folder 70)
    - Beaumont, Betty, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 71)
    - Before Information (Vor der Information): magazine for art, film and theory, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 72)
    - Beiles, Sinclair, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 73)
    - Belden-Sexton-Sumpter Funeral Chapel, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 74)
    - Bell, Hilary, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 75)
    - Bellamy, Dodie, 1987-1992 (Box 1, Folder 76)
    - Benedict, Elizabeth, Undated (Box 1, Folder 77)
    - Bennett, Kim, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 78)
    - Berk, Brett, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 79)
    - Berman, Jenifer, 1997-2005 (Box 1, Folder 80)
    - Bernstein, Karen / Petit Films, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 81)
    - Beyond Baroque: Literary/Arts Center, 1993-2002 (Box 1, Folder 82)
    - Bibel Magazine, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 83)
    - Biblio's Bookstore & Cafe, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 84)
    - Binor, Iris, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 85)
    - Blaise, Paul, [1996] (Box 1, Folder 86)
    - Blake, Nayland, 1997-1999 (Box 1, Folder 87)
    - Blegvad, Peter, 1983-1997 (Box 1, Folder 88)
    - Blind Spot, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 89)
    - Bloom, Barbara, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 90)
    - Bloomberg, Michael R. / The City of New York, Office of the Mayor, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 91)
    - Bloomfield, Nicolas, Undated (Box 1, Folder 92)
    - Bochco, Steven, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 93)
    - Bockris, Victor, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 94)
    - Bolande, Jennifer, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 95)
    - BOMB Magazine, 1990-2001 (Box 1, Folder 96)
    - Book Works / Maria Fusco, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 97)
    - Boothe, Power, 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 98)
    - Border Editions / Sabu Kohso, 1992-1994 (Box 1, Folder 99)
    - Bordowitz, Gregg, 1994-2002 (Box 1, Folder 100)
    - Bornstein, Jenny, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 101)
    - Bouvier, Geoff, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 102)
    - Bowlby, Rachel, 1981-2001 (Box 1, Folder 103)
    - Bowles, Paul / Mohamed Ulad, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 104)
    - Bowman, David, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 105)
    - Bracewell, Michael, 1990-1997 (Box 1, Folder 106)
    - Brainard, Joe, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 107)
    - Breakwell, Ian, 1989-1996 (Box 1, Folder 108)
    - Brennan, Liz, Undated (Box 1, Folder 109)
    - British Film Institute, 1995-1996 (Box 1, Folder 110)
    - Brock, Constance, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 111)
    - Brocksieper, Karl, Undated (Box 1, Folder 112)
    - Brody, Meredith, 1985 - [1994] (Box 1, Folder 113)
    - Bromberg, Craig, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 114)
    - Bronstein, Marcia and Michael, 1984-1993 (Box 1, Folder 115)
    - Brooklyn Museum of Art, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 116)
    - Brought to Book: An anthology edited by Ian Breakwell & Paul Hammond, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 117)
    - Brown, Donald L., 1986 (Box 1, Folder 118)
    - Brown, Mike, 1991-1996 (Box 1, Folder 119)
    - Brown University / Unspeakable Practices III, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 120)
    - Bruggeman, Inge, 1997-2001 (Box 1, Folder 121)
    - Bryant, Elizabeth, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 122)
    - Bui, Thi, 1998-1999 (Box 1, Folder 123)
    - Burgess, Martha, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 124)
    - Burk, Ronnie, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 125)
    - Burkhardt, Rudy, Undated (Box 1, Folder 126)
    - Burstein, Patricia, Undated (Box 1, Folder 127)
    - Burton, Johanna and Tim Griffin, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 128)
    - Bustard, Karen, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 128)
    - Butzin, Dennis, Sophie and Matt, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 130)
    - Butzin, Susan and Don, 19[ ] - 2003 (Box 1, Folder 131)
    - Cabinet, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 132)
    - Cabrera, David P. and Alexander Gray, 1994-1997 (Box 1, Folder 133)
    - Cale, John, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 134)
    - California Institute of the Arts, Division of Critical Studies, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 135)
    - California State University, Sacramento, Department of English, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 136)
    - Callen, Michael, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 137)
    - Calvert, Bob, Undated (Box 1, Folder 138)
    - Cambridge University Press, 1999-2001 (Box 1, Folder 139)
    - Camera Obscura, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 140)
    - Cameron, Peter, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 141)
    - Camille, Megan, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 142)
    - Campbell, Nancy, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 143)
    - Canelon, Peter, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 144)
    - Canongate Books Limited, Undated (Box 1, Folder 145)
    - Cardoni, Ed, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 146)
    - Carey, Ellen, 1995-2006 (Box 1, Folder 147)
    - Carrithers, Robert, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 148)
    - Carter, Charlotte, 1990-2001 (Box 1, Folder 149)
    - Cash, Francis, 1997-1998 (Box 1, Folder 150)
    - Castello di Rivoli, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 151)
    - Catton, Dale, Undated (Box 1, Folder 152)
    - Caveney, Graham, Undated (Box 1, Folder 153)
    - Center on Contemporary Art, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 154)
    - Cesarco, Alejandro, 2001-2002 (Box 1, Folder 155)
    - Cezair-Thompson, Margaret, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 156)
    - Chain, Undated (Box 1, Folder 157)
    - Chaix, Emilie, Undated (Box 1, Folder 158)
    - Chaix (Mathews), Marie, 2000-2001 (Box 1, Folder 159)
    - Champagne, Lenora, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 160)
    - Chant, Benedict, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 161)
    - Charlotte Sheedy Literary Agency, 1987-1990 (Box 1, Folder 162)
    - Charlton, Maryette, 1980-1985 (Box 1, Folder 163)
    - Chase, Cliff, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 164)
    - Cheney, Elyse, Undated (Box 1, Folder 165)
    - Chermayeff, Sasha, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 166)
    - Chester, Laura, 1987-1990 (Box 1, Folder 167)
    - Citibank, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 168)
    - The City of New York, Office of the President of the Borough of Manhattan, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 169)
    - The City University of New York (CUNY), The Center for Lesbian and Gay Studies, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 170)
    - Civitella Ranieri Center, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 171)
    - Clapp, Susannah, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 172)
    - Clark, Emilie, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 173)
    - Clark, S.M., 1994-1995 (Box 1, Folder 174)
    - Clay, Mel, Undated (Box 1, Folder 175)
    - Clinton, Bill, Undated (Box 1, Folder 176)
    - Cockburn, Alex, Undated (Box 1, Folder 177)
    - Coffee House Press, 2003-2004 (Box 1, Folder 178)
    - Cohen, Keith, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 179)
    - Cohen, Liz, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 180)
    - Cohen, Mitch, 1992-1994 (Box 1, Folder 181)
    - Cohen (Koen), Ryosuke, Undated (Box 1, Folder 182)
    - Colaiace, Anna, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Coleman, Les, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Collins, Carol, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Colosi, David, 1995-1997 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Columbia Journalism Review, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Columbia University, 1988-1999 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Community Bookstore of Park Slope, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - The Community Writers' Project Inc., 1991 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Comstock, Rolland L., 1993 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Conditions: a feminist magazine, with an emphasis on writing by lesbians, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Conjunctions, 1989-2001 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Consul General of Belgium in New York, Renilde Loeckx-Drozdiak and William Drozdiak, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Cooke, Geraldine [G.C.] ***see also*** Penguin, Undated (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Cooper, Dennis, 1987-2004 (Box 2, Folder 14)
      General note
      Contains Cooper's e-mail address.
    - Cooper, Jacqueline, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Copyright Clearance Center, Inc., 2005 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Corbett, Bill, 198[0] (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Cornerhouse / Linder Sterling, 2001-2002 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Coromandel Express / Leroy, Gregory, 1999-2002 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Cote, A[lan], 2001 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Council of Literary Magazines and Presses (CLMP), Literary Ventures Fund (LVF), 2005 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - Counter Editions Limited, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Court TV (Courtroom Television Network), 1993 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - Coxhead, David, 1971-1995 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - Coxhead, Gabriel, 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - Coyne, Petah, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - Craig, Randy, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - Crawford, Lynn, 1992-2003 (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - Creative Time, Inc., 1995 (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - Crimp, Douglas, Undated (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - Critical Quarterly, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - Cromwell, Kathy, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 32)
    - Crown Publishers Inc., 1992 (Box 2, Folder 33)
    - CUPS - A Cafe Journal, Undated (Box 2, Folder 34)
    - CUTTING EDGE: The History of Feminist Film and Video, Swarthmore College, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 35)
    - Cypis, (Aya) Doris, 1984-1997 (Box 2, Folder 36)
    - D'Erasam / Porinelli, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 37)
    - Daley, David, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 38)
    - Dalton, David and Coco, 1987-1995 (Box 2, Folder 39)
    - Daniel, David, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 40)
    - Daniels, Leslie, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 41)
    - Dankowski, Jasmina, 1996-1997 (Box 2, Folder 42)
    - Davidson, Robyn, Undated (Box 2, Folder 43)
    - Davidson, Toni, 1988-1998 (Box 2, Folder 44)
    - Davis, Lydia, 1998-2002 (Box 2, Folder 45)
    - Davis, Taylor, Undated (Box 2, Folder 46)
    - Dawson, Jeffrey, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 47)
    - A DAY OF HOPE project / Meg Daly, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 48)
    - de Ridder, Willem, Undated (Box 2, Folder 49)
    - Decision / Stephanie Weh, 2002-2003 (Box 2, Folder 50)
    - Deitcher, David, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 51)
    - DeLynn, Jane, Undated (Box 2, Folder 52)
    - Dene, Perry, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 53)
    - DeShell, Jeffrey George / Fiction Collective Two, 1984-2005 (Box 2, Folder 54)
    - deSouza, Allan, 1994-1998 (Box 2, Folder 55)
    - Deste Foundation, 2000-2002 (Box 2, Folder 56)
    - Detroit Institute of Arts, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 57)
    - Deutsche, Rosalyn, 1995-2002 (Box 2, Folder 58)
    - DeVito, Pop (Oliver) and Helen, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 59)
    - Dewey, Fred, 1994-2008 (Box 2, Folder 60)
    - Dia Center for the Arts, 1991-1996 (Box 2, Folder 61)
    - Dick, Leslie, 1983-1998 (Box 2, Folder 62)
    - Dick, Vivienne, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 63)
    - Dieckmann, Katherine, 1992-2002 (Box 2, Folder 64)
    - Dierbeck, Lisa, 1998-2003 (Box 2, Folder 65)
    - Dieu Donné Papermill Inc., 2002-2003 (Box 2, Folder 66)
    - Dillon, Millicent, 1987-2000 (Box 2, Folder 67)
    - Dinh, Linh ***see also*** Penguin, 1996-1997 (Box 2, Folder 68)
    - D.A.P. (Distributed Art Publishers), Undated (Box 2, Folder 69)
    - District Attorney of the County of New York, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 70)
      Re: Ana Mendieta
    - Divola, John, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 71)
    - Doctors Without Borders, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 72)
    - DOCUMENTS, 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 73)
    - The Dog, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 74)
    - Doggett, David, 1966-1972 (Box 2, Folder 75)
    - Donadio & Ashworth, Inc.: Literary Representatives, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 76)
    - Double Lucy Books / Elizabeth Treadwell, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 77)
    - Dougherty, Cecilia, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 78)
    - Drag City, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 79)